A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, William J. Ronan, Series 29 FA371
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reference Files, 1945-1971; 2; 17.4 Cubic Feet
  - Conservation Department - Forty-ninth Annual Report, 1959, Conservation Department, Harold G. Wilm, Commissioner (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Conservation Department - Fiftieth Annual Report, 1960, Conservation Department, Harold G. Wilm, Commissioner (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Conservation Department - "Now or Never, A Bold New Program for Outdoor Recreation", 1960 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Conservation Department - Outdoor Recreation Survey - A Report of the State of New York Conservation Department, February 1, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Conservation Department - Preliminary Fifty-first Annual Report of the Conservation Department, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Conservation Department - New York State's Conservation Highlights, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Conservation Department - Delta Lake State Park - A Feasibility Study, State of New York Conservation Department, November 1, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Correction Department - 1958 Annual Report, Department of Correction, Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Correction Department - 1959 Annual Report, "Correction and the Young Offender," Department of Correction, Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Correction Department - 1960 Annual Report, Department of Correction, Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Correction Department - 1961 Annual Report, Department of Correction, Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Correction Department - 1962 Annual Report, Department of Correction, Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Department of Health - Basic Vital Statistics, New York State (Exclusive of New York City), 1900-1961, Office of Biostatistics (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Department of Health - New York's Health, 1958 Annual Report, New York State Department of Health, Herman E. Hilleboe, M.D., Commissioner (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Department of Health - New York's Health, 1959 Annual Report, New York State Department of Health, Herman E. Hilleboe, M.D., Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Department of Health - Department Directory, Department of Health, January 1959 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    Published by the Office of Personnel Administration.
  - Department of Health - New York's Health, 1960 Annual Report, New York State Department of Health, Herman E. Hilleboe, M.D., Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Department of Health - New York's Health, 1961 Annual Report, New York State Department of Health, Herman E. Hilleboe, M.D., Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Department of Health - Administrators of Hospitals in New York State, Division of Hospital Review and Planning, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Department of Health - Hospitals, New York State, Division of Hospital Review and Planning, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal - Statistical Summary of Program, June 30, 1964, James Wm. Gaynor, Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal - "The People Decide for Housing," A Report from Joseph P. McMurray, Commissioner of Housing, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal - "An Action Program for Community Development," 1959-1960 Annual Report, New York State Division of Housing, James Wm. Gaynor, Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal - "A Year of Innovation & Growth," 1960-1961 Annual Report, New York State Division of Housing, James Wm. Gaynor, Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal - Statistical Summary of Programs, December 30, 1963, James Wm. Gaynor, Commissioner (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Insurance Department - One-hundredth Preliminary Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the 1959 Legislature for the Calendar Year 1958, Thomas Thacher, Superintendent (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Insurance Department - One Hundredth and First Preliminary Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the 1960 Legislature for the Calendar Year 1959, Thomas Thacher, Superintendent (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Insurance Department - One Hundredth and Second Preliminary Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the New York Legislature for the Calendar Year 1960, Thomas Thacher, Superintendent (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Insurance Department - One Hundredth and Third Preliminary Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the New York Legislature for the Calendar Year 1961, Thomas Thacher, Superintendent (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Insurance Department - The Mortgage Facilities Corporation, December 19, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Labor - 1958 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Isador Lubin (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Labor - Statistics on Operations, Division of Research and Statistics, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Labor - Injury Rates, New York State Industries, Division of Research and Statistics, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Labor - 1959 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Martin P. Catherwood (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Labor - 1960 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Martin P. Catherwood (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Labor - Statistics on Operations, Division of Research and Statistics, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Labor - Wages and Hours in Children's Camps, New York State, Summer 1960, Division of Research and Statistics, June 1961 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Labor - Wages and Hours in Retail Trade, New York State, 1960, Division of Research and Statistics, December 1962 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Labor - The Relation of Family Status to Income and to Participation in the Labor Force, New York State, Division of Research and Statistics, January 1960 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Labor - New York State Collective Bargaining Settlements, Division of Research and Statistics, May 1960 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - Labor - Wages and Hours in Selected Personal Services, New York State, 1960-1961, Division of Research and Statistics, June 1962 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Labor - Wages and Hours in Nonprofit Organizations, New York State, 1961, Division of Research and Statistics, December 1962 (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Labor - Statistics on Operations, Division of Research and Statistics, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Labor - 1961 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Martin P. Catherwood (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Labor - How the New York State Labor Law Protects You, August 1961 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Labor - 1962 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Martin P. Catherwood (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Labor - 1962 Annual Report of the Industrial Commissioner, Martin P. Catherwood, Volume II - Statistical Appendix (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Labor - 1962 Annual Report of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, George J. Mintzer, Chairman (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Labor - Governor's Conference on the Improvement of Occupational Safety, January 10-11, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - Labor - Statistics on Operations, Division of Research and Statistics, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Labor - 1963 Annual Report, New York State Department of Labor, Martin P. Catherwood, Industrial Commissioner (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Labor - 1963 Annual Report, New York State Department of Labor, Martin P. Catherwood, Industrial Commissioner, Volume II - Statistical Appendix (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Labor - Collective Bargaining Settlements in New York State, 1963 Annual Report, June 15, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Labor - Work Stoppages, New York State, Division of Research and Statistics, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Law - 1958 Annual Report of Louis J. Lefkowitz, Attorney General (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Law - 1959 Annual Report, Department of Law, Louis J. Lefkowitz, Attorney General (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Law - 1960 Annual Report, Department of Law, Louis J. Lefkowitz, Attorney General (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Law - Opinions of the Attorney General for the Year Ending December 31, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Mental Hygiene - Sixty-fifth Annual Report of the Department of Mental Hygiene, 1953, Newton Bigelow, M.D., Commissioner (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Mental Hygiene - 1958 Annual Report of the Department of Mental Hygiene, Paul H. Hoch, M.D., Commissioner (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Mental Hygiene - 1960 Statistics of State Mental Hospitals (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Mental Hygiene - 1960 Statistics of State Schools for Mental Defectives and Craig Colony & Hospital (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1954 Annual Report of the Chief of Staff to the Governor for the Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Karl F. Hausauer, Major General, New York National Guard (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1958 Annual Report of the Chief of Staff to the Governor for the Division of Military and Naval Affairs, R. C. Brock, Major General, New York National Guard (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1959 Annual Report of the Chief of Staff to the Governor for the Division of Military and Naval Affairs, A. C. O'Hara, Major General, New York Army Reserve National Guard (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1960 Annual Report of the Chief of Staff to the Governor for the Division of Military and Naval Affairs, A. C. O'Hara, Major General, New York Army Reserve National Guard (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1961 Annual Report, Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Major General A. C. O'Hara, Chief of Staff (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1962 Annual Report, Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Major General A. C. O'Hara, Chief of Staff (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Military and Naval Affairs - 1963 Annual Report, Division of Military and Naval Affairs, Major General A. C. O'Hara, Chief of Staff (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Parole - Twenty-ninth Annual Report of the Division of Parole, 1958, Russell G. Oswald, Chairman (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Parole - Thirtieth Annual Report of the Division of Parole, 1959, Russell G. Oswald, Chairman (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Parole - Thirty-first Annual Report of the Division of Parole, 1960, Russell G. Oswald, Chairman (Box 16, Folder 177)
  - Parole - Facts and Figures of the Division of Parole, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Parole - Thirty-second Annual Report of the Division of Parole, 1961, Russell G. Oswald, Chairman (Box 16, Folder 179)
  - Parole - Thirty-third Annual Report of the Division of Parole, 1962, Russell G. Oswald, Chairman (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Parole - Facts and Figures of the Division of Parole, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Public Service Commission - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1954 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, Benjamin F. Feinberg, Chairman (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Public Service Commission - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1958 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, Benjamin F. Feinberg, Chairman (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Public Service Commission - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1958 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, Benjamin F. Feinberg, Chairman, copy 2 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Public Service Commission - 1959 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Public Service Commission - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1960 Preliminary Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Public Service Commission - 1960 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 17, Folder 187)
  - Public Service Commission - 1961 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Public Service Commission - 1962 Annual Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Public Service Commission - Regulation of Public Utilities in New York State, 1963 Preliminary Report of the Public Service Commission, Department of Public Service, James H. Lundy, Chairman (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - Department of Public Works - 1954 Annual Report of the Superintendent, B. D. Tallamy (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Department of Public Works - 1958 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 18, Folder 192)
  - Department of Public Works - 1959 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - Department of Public Works - New York State's Highway Program, Department of Public Works, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 194)
  - Department of Public Works - 1960 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 18, Folder 195)
  - Department of Public Works - 1960 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran, copy 2 (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - Department of Public Works - 1961 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 18, Folder 197)
  - Department of Public Works - 1962 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - Department of Public Works - 1963 Annual Report of the Superintendent, J. Burch McMorran (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Department of Public Works - 1963 Annual Report of the Superintendent, Statistical Tables, J. Burch McMorran (Box 19, Folder 200)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - 1959 Annual Report, Elmer A. Carter, Chairman (Box 19, Folder 201)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - 1960 Annual Report, Elmer A. Carter, Chairman (Box 19, Folder 202)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - Apprentices, Skilled Craftsmen, and the Negro: An Analysis, April 1960 (Box 19, Folder 203)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - 1961 Annual Report, Ogden Reid, Chairman of SCAD, George Fowler, Chairman of SCHR (Box 19, Folder 204)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - 1961 Annual Report, Ogden Reid, Chairman, Scad, George Fowler, Chairman, SCHR, copy 2 (Box 19, Folder 205)
  - State Commission Against Discrimination/State Commission for Human Rights - 1962 Annual Report, George Fowler, Chairman (Box 19, Folder 206)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Ninety-second Annual Report, 1958, Social Welfare in New York State, Myles B. Amend, Chairman, Board of Social Welfare, Raymond W. Houston, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 207)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Statistical Supplement to Annual Report for 1958, "New York State Social Statistics" (Box 20, Folder 208)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Administrative Cost Study, State of New York Department of Social Welfare, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 209)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Ninety-third Annual Report, 1959, Social Welfare in New York State, Myles B. Amend, Chairman, Board of Social Welfare, Raymond W. Houston, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 210)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Statistical Supplement to Annual Report for 1959, "New York State Social Statistics" (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - Department of Social Welfare - 1960 Annual Report, Public Welfare: A Community Responsibility, Myles B. Amend, Chairman, Board of Social Welfare, Raymond W. Houston, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - Department of Social Welfare - To Prevent and To Restore, a Report on the Rehabilitation Potential of Public Social Services in New York State, February 1960 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - Department of Social Welfare - Statistical Supplement to Annual Report for 1960, "New York State Social Statistics" (Box 20, Folder 214)
  - Department of Social Welfare - 1961 Annual Report, Public Welfare Today, Myles B. Amend, Chairman, Board of Social Welfare, Raymond W. Houston, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 215)
  - Department of Social Welfare - 1962 Annual Report, Recasting Public Welfare in New York State, Myles B. Amend, Chairman, Board of Social Welfare, George K. Wyman, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 216)
  - Department of Social Welfare - 1963 Annual Report, Major Developments in Public Welfare, George K. Wyman, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 217)
  - Department of Social Welfare - 1963 Preliminary Annual Report, Major Developments in Public Welfare, George K. Wyman, Commissioner, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 20, Folder 218)
  - State Department - 1954 Annual Report of the Department of State, Carmine G. DeSapio, Secretary of State (Box 20, Folder 219)
  - State Department - 1958 Annual Report of the Department of State, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State (Box 20, Folder 220)
  - State Department - 1959 Annual Report of the Department of State, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State (Box 20, Folder 221)
  - State Department - 1960 Annual Report of the Department of State, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - State Department - 1960 Annual Report of the Department of State, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State, copy 2 (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - State Department - 1961 Annual Report of the Department of State, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State (Box 21, Folder 224)
  - State Department - 1962 Annual Report of the Department of State, Serving the Public, Caroline K. Simon, Secretary of State (Box 21, Folder 225)
  - State Department - State Bingo Control Commission Annual Report, 1962, Ira M. Ball, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 226)
  - State Department - State Bingo Control Commission Annual Report, 1963, Ira M. Ball, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 227)
  - State Department - 1954 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 228)
  - State Department - 1958 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 229)
  - State Department - 1959 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 230)
  - State Department - The New York Racing Association, Inc., Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 231)
  - State Department - 1960 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 232)
  - State Department - 1961 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 233)
  - State Department - 1962 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 234)
  - State Department - 1963 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 235)
  - State Department - 1964 Annual Report of the New York State Racing Commission to the Secretary of State, Ashley Trimble Cole, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 236)
  - State Department - 1959 Annual Report of the New York State Harness Racing Commission, Robert A. Glasser, Chairman (Box 21, Folder 237)
  - State Police - Forty-first Annual Report of the New York State Troopers, 1958, Francis S. McGarvey, Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 238)
  - State Police - Forty-second Annual Report of the New York State Troopers, 1959, Francis S. McGarvey, Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 239)
  - State Police - Forty-third Annual Report of the New York State Troopers, 1960, Arthur Cornelius, Jr., Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 240)
  - State Police - 1961 Annual Report, New York State Police, Arthur Cornelius, Jr., Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 241)
  - State Police - 1962 Annual Report, New York State Police, Arthur Cornelius, Jr., Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - State Police - 1963 Annual Report, New York State Police, Arthur Cornelius, Jr., Superintendent (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - 1957-1958 Annual Report of the State Tax Commission, George M. Bragalini, Commissioner of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - Planning Report for 1958, Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 245)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - 1958-1959 Annual Report of the State Tax Commission, Joseph H. Murphy, Commissioner of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 246)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - Planning Report for 1959, Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 247)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - 1959-1960 Annual Report of the State Tax Commission, Joseph H. Murphy, Commissioner of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 248)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - Planning Report for 1960, Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 249)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - 1960-1961 Annual Report of the State Tax Commission, Joseph H. Murphy, Commissioner of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 250)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - Planning Report for 1961, Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 251)
  - Department of Taxation and Finance - Planning Report for 1962, Department of Taxation and Finance (Box 22, Folder 252)
  - Division of Youth - 1959 Annual Report of the New York State Youth Commission, Mark A. McCloskey, Chairman (Box 22, Folder 253)
  - Division of Youth - 1960 Annual Report, Division of Youth, Alexander Aldrich, Chairman (Box 22, Folder 254)
  - Division of Youth - 1961 Annual Report, Division of Youth, Alexander Aldrich, Chairman (Box 22, Folder 255)
  - Division of Youth - The School Dropout Problem in Major Cities of New York State, Rochester - Part 1, May 1962 (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - Division of Youth - The School Dropout Problem in Major Cities of New York State, Buffalo - Part 1, July 1963 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Division of Youth - Youth in Two Rural Counties of New York State: A Survey Conducted in Schoharie and Greene Counties, August 1963 (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Division of Veterans Affairs - 1958 Annual Report, Frank V. Votto, Director (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - Division of Veterans Affairs - 1959 Annual Report, Frank V. Votto, Director (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Division of Veterans Affairs - 1960 Annual Report, Frank V. Votto, Director (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Division of Veterans Affairs - 1961 Annual Report, Frank V. Votto, Director (Box 23, Folder 262)
  - Division of Veterans Affairs - 1963 Annual Report, Frank V. Votto, Director (Box 23, Folder 263)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - Compensated Cases Closed, 1950-1954, Part 3 - Occupation, S. E. Senior, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 264)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - Summary of Board Activities, 1957, Angela R. Parisi, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 265)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - Compensated Cases Closed, 1959, S. E. Senior, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 266)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - Summary of Board Activities, 1960, S. E. Senior, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 267)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - "Path to a New Life, the Story of Rehabilitation," November 1961 (Box 23, Folder 268)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board - Summary of Board Activities, 1962, S. E. Senior, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 269)
  - Local Government - 1959-1960 Annual Report, Office for Local Government, Frank C. Moore, Chairman (Box 23, Folder 270)